{
    "questions": [
    {
        "question": "Where does the name Raspberry Pi come from?",
        "answers": [
            "The board is the color of a raspberry.",
            "From the fruit naming tradition of microcomputers + Python.",
            "It is Eben Upton's favorite type of dessert."
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the browser that comes installed on a Raspberry Pi?",
        "answers": [
            "Midori",
            "Raspbrowser",
            "Chromium"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "How many USB connections are on the Raspberry Pi?",
        "answers": [
            "1",
            "2",
            "None"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What directories are searched if a PYTHONPATH is set in an env?",
        "answers": [
            "PYTHONPATH directory",
            "Current directory",
            "home directory",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Where did Python get it's name from?",
        "answers": [
            "It sounded cool",
            "Guido Van Rossum's pet python",
            "Monty Python's Flying Circus"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "In Python, what number is associated with the first item in a list of items?",
        "answers": [
            "1",
            "0"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of these is NOT a Python web framework?",
        "answers": [
            "Django",
            "Flask",
            "Twisted",
            "Pyramid"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "True or False? PEP8 calls for 4 spaces for code indentation.",
        "answers": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the PEP8, what is the max number of characters allowed per line.",
        "answers": [
            "140",
            "42",
            "79"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "At PyCon 2013, all of the attendees received a:",
        "answers": [
            "Raspberry Pi + SD card + power cord",
            "Python book",
            "A pony"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the person who invented Python?",
        "answers": [
            "Tim Berners-Lee",
            "Guido van Rossum",
            "Steve Jobs"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the difference between a tuple and a list?",
        "answers": [
            "A tuple uses dots to concatenate items, while a list does not.",
            "Tuples cannot be changed while lists can.",
            "Tuples are a kind of flower. You are being silly."
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What would the following statement print? b = 2  a = 1 + b print a",
        "answers": [
            "3",
            "1b",
            "a"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    }
    ]
}